Coding this prototype was a great challenge to demonstrate the techniques we’ve accumulated over the semester, and I am proud to have successfully applied the following into a responsive website:

> HTML & CSS file setup and boilerplate code
> HTML tags, boxes and content
> CSS selectors, styling including margins, padding, colour, font style, and a taste of animation
> Layout, display(flex, block, inline-block, none), position (relative, absolute)
> Standard media query widths, text sizes, and line heights.

The biggest challenge was the interaction of each section with the other because of the several layout mechanisms being used and manipulated according to screen size—and happily, according to my code!

Though intimidating to design, everything seemed to come together in the planning and sketching phase. Drawing and identifying the various lessons and techniques we could apply was extremely helpful in both better understanding those techniques and how they would work in the context of our prototype. Once everything was drawn out, it was a matter of writing and tweaking the code to appear and interact how it was envisioned in the sketches. I am very happy with the result and confident in my ability to apply this learning.

In the context of my level of experience, I believe an A+ would be a fair grade because of how the prototype works, and how much work went into it. I was committed (35 commits!) to making a page with flow and responsiveness on any screen size. Although spending an obscene amount of time coding, the prototype responded how I wanted early on, so extra time was spent having fun with more style. 

My level of experience, however, means I have yet to fully grasp the intricacies of HTML and CSS; and though displaying properly and responsively, there likely exists more practical means of achieving the same results. For that reason—and not being able to get these words out quite by midnight— a different grade may be more suitable, and I welcome the learning experience.

Thank you @thomasjbradley
